

- manuelfer912@gmail.com
- 229-23 Jangjeon-dong, Geumjeong-gu, Busan
- Date of birth 12/09/1994
- +821073022612
- Single 3
- Peruvian

Languages

Spanish

English

> IELTS: 6.5/9

Korean

TOPIK, level 3

Skills

Imaginative Thinking

Patience

Adaptability

Leadership Skills

Highly Organized

Ability to Work in a Team

Computer Skills

Communication Skills

Fast Learner

Ability to Multitask

Critical thinking and problem solving

Manuel FLORES

A highly motivated and hard-working Mechanical engineering in mechanical system design graduate with an interest in entrepreneurship and a great passion for scientific and technological research. Has 1+ years of experience teaching and Translating English

Education

Master of Science in Mechanical Engineering

Pusan National University, Busan, South Korea Since February 2022

GPA: 4.17/4.5

Former of Latin American student Association in PNU

Bachelor of Science in Mechanical Engineering

State University of Callao, Lima, Peru From August 2012 to July 2017

GPA: 3.0/4.0

- Graduated in 4th place with over 65 students.
- Awarded first place in a football competition twice.

Work experience

Research Assistant

PUSAN NATIONAL UNIVERSITY, Busan, South Korea Since February 2022

- · Non-destructive inspection of metal plates using ultrasound
- Application of deep learning in ultrasonic tomography image
- Chief Technology Officer

KYP BIOENGINEERING, Lima, Peru From June 2017 to August 2020

- Research, fabricate, and test mechanisms and electronics of low-cost 3D printers, and low-cost prosthetic hand

Research Assistant

AVIATION OF THE PERUVIAN ARMY, Lima, Peru

From August 2016 to November 2017

- Assisted in the project "Satélite Sondeo Distancia a Tierra".
- Fabricated an inexpensive mini tractor to facilitate farmers 'work.
- Facilitated the relationship between the Peruvian army with public universities in Peru.

Computer skills

MS Excel, Ms Word, Ms Powerpoint

Simplify 3D, Cura, Meshmixer

3D printing

Autodesk Inventor, Fusion360

3D Design

Inventor HSM CAM

CAM

Python

Data Analysis Computer Vision Deep Learning

Interests

Sport or Hobby

· Football player

Extra-curricular Activities

Private teacher of Mathematics, Physics, and English, Freelance Since January 2015

- Provided students with in-home English, math, and physics tutoring, instructional support, homework assistance, and exam preparation.
- Customized Tutoring and instructional approaches to meet the needs of the students.